Marya Jabar Mohamad

marya.jabar.m@gmail.com | (+964)774 152 0880 | Sulaymaniyah, Iraq

Profile

I am an enthusiastic and motivated business IT graduate with successful experience in social media management, and design, online sales. I strive to create an impact in my field and secure challenging and responsible positions to expand my learning, knowledge, and skills.

Education

University of Sulaymaniyah, College of Commerce

2018 - 2022

• Bachelor of Science in Information Technology (IT)

Experience

Social Media Manager at KarsazyShadman page, Sulaymaniyah, Iraq Aug 2023 – May 2024

- Designed engaging social media posts and using Adobe Photoshop.
- Interacted with customers and provided customer service to address inquiries and solve problems.
- Responded promptly to messages, fostering community engagement.
- Developed a comprehensive Point of Sale (POS) system using C# and SQL Server

Social Media Manager, Healthy Kids (Remote)

Apr 2023 – Mar 2024

- Designed engaging social media posts and edited captivating videos using Adobe Photoshop and Capcut.
- Responded promptly to messages, fostering community engagement.
 Managed sponsored content partnerships, enhancing brand visibility and reach.

Hard Skills

- Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator and Canva.
- Excellent data entry.
- Proficiency in google Apps (docs, sheets, slides, google meet, google calendar, class room, Gmail, google drive).
- Proficiency in Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, PowerPoint).

- Strong SQL development skills.
- Computer Software Knowledge.
- Proficiency in Web development (html, Css, Bootstrap, Ajax, Php,Laravel).
- Proficiency in C# language.
- Understanding of database principles, structures, theories and practices. Computer Software Knowledge.

Soft Skills

- Excellent teamworking skills (easily adapt with co-workers to accomplish common goals).
- Excellent negotiations skills and communication skills.
- Excellent time management skills (prioritizing deadlines for given tasks, punctual within workforce).
- Work well under pressure.
- Conflict resolutions (problem solver by nature) communication skills.

Certification & Qualification

Certification of Completion for 160-Hour course in Social Media Marketing and Graphic Design Workwell Organization	2023
Certification of Completion for Professional Developing Microsoft Excel Skills German Centre, Migration and Reintegration, Iraq (GMAC)	2022
Certification of Completion for 160-Hour course in Business IT and English Workwell Organization	2022
Certification of steps to run a new project	2021
University of Sulaymaniyah	
Certification of English course for the intermediate level	2020
Online Course-Mohamad Mahdi	

Languages

- Fluent In Kurdish (Sorani)
- Intermediate English